Hi guys in this video I will compare
two traditional health insurances that
I think are quite interesting from
Prudential and from Manulife Well I
made this video so that you can be more
clear glue clearly How to compare
one product with another my name
is the choice and I am a
file-file I often share about
mp3boss Finance investment insurance
whatever it is on my Instagram So if
for example you want to learn
more you can follow
my Instagram we will start directly from the
product the product is called
Manulife naik Ultimate Health Care or
kykx with Prudential PSS or
healthy solutions this is quite interesting circle
both of them are
traditional insurance traditional mix double
investment at all if for example I
may beg a little bit Manulife
has always had many traditional products
while it has always been
more of these products but in the
last few years Prudential has
issued many traditional products
and Finally found this ultimate
help care with PSS we want to know
which one is more suitable for you
starting from the price first for the
price comparison from Manulife it is 463
thousand three hundred per month and from
Prudential is 350 2014, I
took the price for a man aged
30 years and both of them don't
smoke because of the two
caddy's, this is still the case if
we look at it from the price alone, it's
clear that Prudential is
superior, but if we can buy
goods, it's not just a fairy tale price,
we see, right, we also see
what the Bali is or what the benefits are, are they
really useful for us or not, which one is
suitable, it's not always
contacted with the price Okay, we'll
continue, look at the others too Okay, next
is the coverage area Well, with the
price of 463 300, Manulife protects the
insured, namely in Indonesia and
Malaysia, but if for example from
Prudential itself, this area is known to be
only in Indonesia, meaning here
Manulife is superior, but again,
you think about it,
if for example you need this insurance
just for eh I'm afraid if
for example you end up being
hospitalized because of dengue fever because of
all kinds of UJS, that's a disease that
I think is very dangerous in
Indonesia, if for example like that,
I think maybe there's no
need to go to Malaysia for treatment
Yes, if for example you have to go to
Malaysia for treatment, usually it's a
pretty serious illness, source, well, it
depends on your age. In my opinion, if
for example, your grave is still
25-30 years old and you assume that
for example I need this insurance only
to cover me for
diseases that are admitted to the hospital,
Dengue, Appendicitis, or whatever, and it's
better to be treated in Indonesia. Well, that
means Prudential is still better,
but if for example, in terms of
coverage area alone, then Manulife is
better because Manulife can cover Indonesia and
Malaysia for the cost of the room itself, it's
actually the same, 500,000 or a double
standard room, where the
Prudential factor is also the same, so in some
benefits between Manulife and this code, there are
actually many that are the same and I
won't discuss it in this video because
according to me there are no files either, well,
I will discuss which ones are different and
which ones are superior and which ones are less superior, the
benefits of rooms outside
Malaysia and Indonesia are multiplied by three
from the BKB of rooms in Indonesia. We all
know that for example, if you
go to Singapore for treatment in Indonesia, the price is different.
If in Indonesia in Jakarta, it
might be one and a half million to one million
per room.  Alone Yang
Yang single standard room but for
example in Singapore it can be
many times more foam 67 additional in
manulai itself give and effect like
this which is three times the cost of the
room here Indonesia and Malaysia Okay
next is the cost of Ecu both of them are the same
Askar also during nasi kucing planet
but in Prudential this is given a maximum of
how many days produced by given a
maximum of 150 days per year while in
Manulife it is Amen in the police I smack
March there is no limit on how many days
so in this position Manulife wins again
Lex is a general practitioner visit In
Manulife it is only once per day but
in Prudential it is a maximum of 1 times
per day well here Prudential is
superior next is the cost of care by
nurses So if for example a
patient is discharged from the hospital and then
needs a nurse to take care of
see Well here
the benefits are also given but they are different Manulife
is 200 thousand per day but if for example
Prudential is echs so it is not
limited to how many hundreds of thousands
per day but is given a limit of 120
days per year Well in my opinion here
because es  My gold charts I DC is
superior next is the cost of physiotherapy
if for example in Manulife It is covered 250
Rp hi but if for example in
Prudential it is not only the cost of
physiotherapy but also
occupational therapy and speech therapy so it is more
complete with a maximum of Saturday visits
per day for all between fires a maximum of
30 days before hospitalization during
hospitalization and 90 days after
hospitalization a maximum of 90 days per year Well
because it is more complete and this is also
according to me MPASI Prudential is
superior here okay besides that there is also something
called [ __ ] and form if
for example a child Usually if
for example admitted to the hospital there must be someone to
accompany or if possible parents
must also love Accompany both of them
But unfortunately if for example
Manulife is only the child's responsibility
he was brought 17 years old Well that is given a
quota of 500,000 per day but if
Prudential 600 thousand per day a maximum of 150
days per year and the insured is
not only the child So if for example the
chairman continues to be lower like that Must
accompany there  because he can't
because there has to be someone to look after him, it's still
replaced by Prudential with a
maximum of 600 thousand per day here, it's clear to
me that the product is superior because there is no
age limit, even if he is 15, 30,
45, 75, whatever it is, if he survives, he is the
insured, then his companion
can still be covered by them. Okay, next,
there are the costs of breast reconstruction surgery
and facial reconstruction. Well, there is a
difference between these two things, for
example, breast reconstruction is three
months after the mastectomy, covered by
Manulife, but if it's Prudential, it's
six months. After the comic period, so for
six months, if for example, he
wants surgery within these six months, it's
still covered, but if it's
facial reconstruction, it's 30 days after the accident, at
Manulife, the funds are months since the surgical procedure
due to cancer or demi-production cells, in
my opinion, Prudential is also superior here,
okay, if for example, you're still watching
this far, maybe you'll see that, for
example, Prudential is
cheaper but has more benefits,
it's superior, we have to see
when this product will appear, predictions.
This is still a new product, like 1.5 years
ago, as far as I remember, but if
Manulife is about 4.5 years Sorry, it
means rejecting longer already Sel is
still fresher, usually a
fresher product is
an improvement on the existing product
and usually if for example you
buy a cellphone, it's still iPhone iPhone
11 and not, they
compete with each other and if they come out
with the same It's impossible, it
seems like we have to be
fresher too, which one is because
fresher Prudential usually
Prudential will
improve the product more, okay, well, if
for example you get beryllium
so far, don't forget to subscribe
and don't forget to like this video and comment
if for example you have questions, let's
just continue, for example, if you
see we take the benefits of Prudential,
there is something called third-party donor cost reimbursement
Well, if compared to
Manulife, Manulife doesn't immediately
give a table, it doesn't immediately give the
benefits, it appears, but it's actually
hidden in the additional benefits, yes,
additional benefits, namely, for example, the
lowest plan is six
billion, but it applies in the first 12 months
since the verdict compared to Prudential, which is
Escalade, maybe if for example I
may, this is a bit balanced like this I
can't say
which is superior because  similar, it's just hidden,
actually, what
Kenek has is the benefit of
daily care compensation. So, for example, in
Manulife, you are given 400 thousand per day
for a maximum of 30 days, while in Prudential, you
get 500,000 per day for a maximum of 100 days
per year. Hi, if the cost of hospitalization
has been paid by the program and
insurance or other insurance. So, for
example, if you have government BPJS
for hospitalization, you can still
go here, Prudential Manulife is a duet like
that, but in this case,
Prudential adds more spice because it's
more, 500,000 per day and a maximum of
100,100 days per year. Lex is the cost of
school assessment. Well, in Manulife, it
still covers one million per year, the amount is
not large, but at least it's still more.
You compared to professionals, there's nothing at
all.
Okay, for emergency outpatient costs
due to accidents. So, if, for example,
you fall and so on,
maybe you get injured or torn or whatever,
Prudential's friends actually
cover it, but if, for example, Manulife
can only cover it within the next 24 hours,
but if, for example,
Prudential  48 hours or two days
means in those two days you have to be
able to report to the doctor Why did you have
an accident and all sorts and Hi
receive treatment it is still covered but
if for example Manulife is only one day
in this case Prudential is again
superior Besides that XL also you are
a nun continued because the accident is
valid 30 days after Jaka other types
48 hours there are also 30 days
after the accident well this writes there is nothing
at all meaning
emergency outpatient costs because the accident is only
covered 24 hours After he had an accident in
this case Prudential is also superior
insurance has benefits that
convert patients This is if for example
he had treatment before hospitalization
and has been hospitalized but must be
related to Why was hospitalized
for example this patient maybe he has dengue fever
usually before Canada blood test and
to the doctor and all sorts until
diagnosed with dengue fever finally admitted to the hospital
Then after he is discharged from the hospital
must check again don't this is the same
cover style as Manulife and
Prudential but for in the case of Manulife
for treatment After he stayed
60 days after discharge if
Shippuden sel 90 days after he was discharged
Well so here Prudential  also
superior Okay in Prudential there is a
Man benefit fee for this office for
a maximum of five years after
active treatment Manulife is not hungry
but it covers it in additional benefits
for colon cancer and all
sorts of things that apply for 6m valid
but only in the first 12 months well
here Prudential is also superior
because it covers five years after
active treatment In Manulife there is a
diagnostic test fee that is
mari1mas all sorts even though we
see the benefits are patched, the production
is there but actually this is included in the
outpatient care before hospitalization I
've checked with the police, it turns out there is also that the
same 30 days before
hospitalization for Manulife in Prudential is the
hospitalization this means the same dental care costs are
also the same for dental care for In
Manulife it is in a hospital or dental clinic
not in the Prudential benefits table
it is not there but it is included
in emergency outpatient care only for
accidents and continued emergency outpatient care
only to finish it is
actually the same so both are equal
even though Prudential does not put this
in its table for funeral benefits
So if for example
this patient is treated in a hospital in  cover
with the author or XL but
it turns out he died then he will be given
funeral benefits from Manulife that is
30 million from Prudential that is 15 million in
this case Manulife is still superior
Hi besides that there is also a benefit called
ecive or X compensation that is 15
million if for example in Prudential In
Manulife This is
ucafe coverage or X 30 million after 12 months of
waiting period so this is similar but
bigger In Manulife Well for the
annual benefit is actually the same 2m for the
other the smallest this is the lowest
this is the production and nuclear bonus
means if for example the insured does not claim the
benefit for the
children's year is 10% so from the second two point 2 the
second year for example he is no longer glue
then it increases to 2.4 the third year
the cream becomes 22.6 well up to the maximum
is an increase of 50% meaning this annual benefit has the
potential to continue to increase to 3
m with several conditions that
are there are no claims in that year so
he gets 10% Okay Saturday yes second is the
accumulation is more or less or the same
with 10% of the initial annual benefit
to 2m So if for example
someone has more than 200 million from
two mwc 10% that means the nuclear bonus
can not be clicked like that later
it means he will just lock there well then so
never also then the
maximum is 50% of the
initial annual insurance benefit Okay besides that
there is also the
PSS limit Booster which is 8m if
for example in this planning well
this amount will be useful if for example
the patient has clicked 2m
then it turns out to be more than
2m he will eat Simi poster
the difference is if for example every year
this Booster limit is not renewed So
if for example the big tip is used 523
this is seven and a half m
next year that is 2m five years which
will return again 7 hands will still
be that well in terms of
annual benefits in my opinion still go to the workshop
first because it has the potential to
increase up to 50% total from 2m this
means around three okay that's all the video
from me Hopefully this can help you
more clearly about which porak is more
suitable for you Manulife may be more
expensive but he  can cover up to
Malaysia but Prudential is cheaper
but with some by David who wrote there is
nothing okay Which one do you like
please comment below and don't forget to
subscribe and like this video if
for example this can help you
in doing anything cave Phillip
month saying of March
Hi porno